我对这顿晚饭好期待啊
Oh, I'm so excited for this dinner.
是啊 但是你俩
Yeah, hey, how did you two
是怎么在Rolin and Jones订到位子的
get reservations to Rolin and Jones anyway?
我听说已经排到一年后了
I heard there was a one-year wait.
其实挺好订的
No, no, it was easy.
那里的厨师追尾了我们的车 我们没叫警察
The chef rear-ended us and we didn't call the police.
他说他喝了一点点烹调酒
Yeah, he said he'd just had a little bit of cooking wine,
不过我能看到他鼻子呼出的可卡因
but I could see some cooking cocaine around his nose.
你俩不尴尬吧
This isn't awkward for you guys, is it?
还是分手后太快再聚在一起了
Because it's so soon after your break-up?
- 没有 - 没有
- No! - No, no.
我们约会前就是朋友
I mean, we were friends before we were dating,
我们觉得我们还能做朋友
so we thought we can do that again.
- 是的 - 是的
- Yeah. - Yeah.
你们有没有人注意到
Have any of you noticed
我们已经五分钟
we haven't moved
没有动过了
in five minutes?
- 没有动过 - 是的
- No. - Hmm.
可能出事故了
Must be an accident.
我去看一下
Yeah, I'll go check it out.
反正我也要去小便
I got to pee anyway.
车库
How's, uh,
怎么样
the garage?
- 很暖和 - 很冷
- Warm. - Cozy?
- 很暖和 - 是的
- Yeah, warm? - Yeah.
他们可不是朋友
Hey, they're not friends.
你说什么呢 他俩很好啊
What are you talking about? They're fine.
不好意思 他俩不可能是朋友
Exes, they can't be friends.
你不接
You getting a call?
我过会儿回过去
I'll call back.
没事的 你可以出去接的
Nah, it's okay. You can take it outside.
我的意思是 不关我们的事
I mean, none of our business, right?
没事的
No, it... it's fine.
没事
It's fine.
很有趣吧
Is it fine?
好吧
All right, well,
看来得等一阵子了
looks like this is gonna take a while.
总统在这附近做募捐
They got a bunch of streets blocked off
他们封锁了几条街道
because the president's having a fund-raiser in the area.
我猜特勤局
And I guess the Secret Service apparently
对站街的玩笑已经不感兴趣了
doesn't like hooker jokes anymore.
这太有趣了 我觉得很有趣
Well, this is fun. I'm having fun.
是的 特别有趣
Yeah, so-so fun.
- 很有趣 - 我好饿啊
- So fun. - I am so hungry.
我后备箱的救急箱里面
Hey, I've got granola bars
有燕麦棒
in the emergency kit back there!
- 太好了 - 太好了 Heather
- Oh, yes. - Yes, Heather!
我已经三天没吃饭了
I haven't eaten in, like, three days...
拿出来 拿出来
Oh, get' em out, get' em out.
大餐啊
waiting for this dinner.
我欠你一条燕麦棒 Tim
"I. O. U. One granola bar. Tim."
我欠你
Uh, "I. O. U.
一条燕麦棒
One granola bar.
Tim
Tim."
我欠你一卷卫生纸
"I. O. U. A toilet paper.
Tim
Tim."
好吧
Oh, you know what?
我这次要接了
Uh, I better take it this time.
你好
Hello.
- 很奇怪 - 怎么了
- That's weird. - Yeah?
要开始了
Here it comes.
我打算假装在读操作指南
I'm just gonna pretend to read this manual.
电话太私人了还得出去接
It's so private she has to take it outside?
是吗
Right?
我是说
I'm just saying
这对你们来说太没礼貌了 不是吗
that's rude to you guys, right?
我是说 当你坐到一个车里面
I mean, 'cause when... when you get into a car with people,
有一条不成文的规定就是
there's a sort of unwritten contract
你得跟人们一起呆在车里
that you're gonna stay in the car with the people,
忠于这辆车和车里面的人
be loyal to the car and-and the people,
而不是出门离开这辆车
and not, like, get out and walk away from a car.
这辆车有车载WIFI热点
Oh, hey, uh, this car's got its own Wi-Fi hotspot.
- 是的 - 你知道吗
- Yeah. - You know what?
我还得去小便
I got to whizz again.
我有个猫头鹰的膀胱
I go the bladder of an owl,
我想应该是很小的吧
which I imagine's pretty small.
这是真的
Man, that's true.
坐个电梯的时间他都憋不住
Even elevator rides are very difficult for him.
还好吗
Everything okay?
- 还好 - 还好
- Yeah, fine. - Yeah, good.
只是个朋友
That was just a friend?
不是吧 Matt 你真想知道我跟谁打电话
Really, Matt? You really need to know who I was talking to?
- 不想知道 -是吗
- No, I don't. - Hmm.
- 是的 不关我事 - 好吧
- No, it's none of my business. - Okay.
- 是不关你事 - 我只是觉得
- Nope. - I mean, is it rude
跟朋友和家人一起出去的时候
to get out of a car
到车外面接电话
and take a phone call, you know, w... when you're hanging out
是很没有礼貌的
with your friend and his family? I don't know.
天知地知你知我知
That's between you and the Lord.
Heather 车载WIFI的密码是什么
Hey, uh, Heather, what is the, uh, the WiFi password here?
我要看一些划水失败的视频
I want to watch some, uh, waterslide fail videos.
密码是HotforHeater69
It's, uh, it's, uh, HotforHeater69.
我想起来低血糖Matt了
Oh, I remember Low Blood Sugar Matt.
- 你记得他 是吗 - 是啊
- You remember this guy? Do you? - Yeah.
- 是吗 - 记得很清楚
- Yeah? - Real well.
他跟你爸像吗
Is he anything like your dad?
因为如果有相似点的话 也许你应该跟他分手
Cause if he is, you should probably break up with him.
这就是他跟我分手的原因
See, that's why she broke up with me.
- 天啊 - 你们俩
- Wow. - Hey, you guys,
看看这个
can I draw your attention to this?
看这个地图
Check out this map.
我能缩小到能看到Hawwii呢
I can zoom all the way over to Hawaii. Look.
你知道吗 Matt
You know what, Matt? This is not the time
现在的时间和地点都不适合讨论这个
or the place to get into this.
- 不适合吗 -不适合
- Is it not? - No, it's not.
是吗 你的小朋友打回来了么
No. Is your little friend calling back?
他不是我的小朋友
He's not my little friend.
- 所以是个男的了 - 是啊
- No, but... so it is a he? - Mm-hmm.
- 他不小 - 喂
- And he's not little? - Hey!
你吃什么呢
What did you just eat?
- 没什么 - 张开嘴
- Nothing. - Open it.
- 你吃什么呢 - 走开
- What are you eating? - Go away!
好了我承认
Stop, I'll tell!
我在外套里找到一片
I found one of Lark's teething biscuits
Lark的磨牙饼干
in my jacket.
什么
What?
有一半是我的 还给我
That's half mine! Give me that.
想喂小鸟一样喂给我
Spit it into my mouth like a baby bird.
你知道吗
You know what? I thought that
我以为跟你做朋友比什么都不是好点
being friends with you would actually be better
但并不是 这感觉太糟了
than nothing, but... news flash... it isn't. This sucks.
你以为跟你做朋友像公园散步那么简单
You think being friends with you is a walk in the park?
你的性格太消极抵抗了
You are so passive-aggressive
有时我都分不清
that sometimes I can't tell
我是在跟你说话还是跟你妈说话
if I'm talking to you or your mother.
别提我妈
No, you did not just bring my mother into this!
我就说
I said your mother,
因为你知道我是对的
because you know it's true!
我提她
I did bring her up...
- 是因为她和你 - 天啊
- because she and you... - Oh, my goodness gracious.
我觉得有时候我们在交谈
I feel like sometimes we're talking at each other.
但你从来不听
You never listen.
天啊
Oh, God... !
这好像是我有过的最糟的主意
This is, like, the worst idea I've ever had in my...
我们永远不可能做朋友
We could never be friends!
- 太悲哀了 - 是啊
- So sad. - Oh, I know.
他们以前在一起的时候多好
They were so good together.
不好
No.
我把另一半磨牙饼干落在车里了
I left half of the teething biscuit in the car.
出发了
Okay, here we go!
车动了 可以走了
Wait, cars are moving. Cars are moving!
出发了
We're moving!
说不定我们还能赶上我们的预约时间呢
Oh, hey! Maybe we can still make our reservation.
- 是的 - Tim去哪了
- Yeah. - Where's Tim?
- Tim -Tim
- Tim! - Tim?
不行 我不能没有味觉
Oh, no, no, no. I can't lose my sense of smell.
这是我们与动物的一大区别
That's what separates us from the animals.